老佛爷lfy\h\h\hKathie228\h\h\h\h莲花葬在深海\h\h\h\hBlack丶
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
Junosis\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
Keep your hands up, keep your hands up.
手抬起来  手抬起来
♪ How could you ever know When you look at me ♪
♪ 当你看着我时  你又怎么知道 ♪
♪ That I've been through enough Challenge for a century? ♪
♪ 我经历了一个世纪的挑战 ♪
♪ Both physically And mentally ♪
♪ 身体上和精神上都有 ♪
♪ This shit will catch up with me ♪
♪ 麻烦会跟上我 ♪
♪ Pin me down and render me ♪
♪ 把我绑起  最后让我 ♪
♪ Incapacitated eventually ♪
♪ 丧失能力 ♪
♪ I hate it It'll be the end of me ♪
♪ 我讨厌这会是我的末日 ♪
♪ And this is for certain This is not potentially ♪
♪ 不是可能  而是一定的 ♪
♪ It's deadly, the way I'm Breaking down so steadily ♪
♪ 这是致命的  我的精神不断崩溃 ♪
♪ Though you see me smiling Though you hear me jokin'♪
♪ 虽然你看到我在笑  听到我在开玩笑 ♪
♪ Though I keep shining You would--♪
♪ 虽然我在一直闪耀  你会 ♪
Hi Kamura.
嗨  卡姆拉
What are you doing on the table?
你在桌子上干什么
You're not supposed to be on the table.
你不该上桌子
♪ I'm just hanging on Hanging on ♪
♪ 我只是在坚持 ♪
♪ Through the night Through the night ♪
♪ 从黑夜  从黑夜 ♪
♪ To the dawn To the dawn ♪
♪ 直到黎明  直到黎明 ♪
♪ And I'm just tryna make it Tryna make it ♪
♪ 我只是试着去  试着去 ♪
♪ One more night One more night ♪
♪ 再熬过一夜  再过一夜 ♪
♪ I see the light ♪
♪ 我看到了光 ♪
♪ They say what doesn't Kill you only makes you strong ♪
♪ 他们说杀不死你的只会让你变强 ♪
♪ They had it easy They got it wrong ♪
♪ 他们想的太简单  他们弄错了 ♪
♪ What if it breaks you down 'Til a piece of you is gone ♪
♪ 如果它让你崩溃直到部分的你消失 ♪
♪ I'll never move on ♪
♪ 我无法再前进 ♪
♪ I've been changed in a way That I'll never be the same ♪
♪ 我已经被改变了  我将不再是原来的我 ♪
♪ I pray every day just to get Me through this pain ♪
♪ 我每天都祈祷能让我度过这痛苦 ♪
♪ I try to lift me up I try to pick me up ♪
♪ 我试着挺起来  试着振作起来 ♪
♪ I been through it all but I Ain't never giving up ♪
♪ 我经历了这一切  但我从未放弃 ♪
♪ I'm just hanging on Hanging on ♪
♪ 我只是在坚持 ♪
♪ Through the night Through the night ♪
♪ 从黑夜  从黑夜 ♪
♪ To the dawn To the dawn ♪
♪ 直到黎明  直到黎明 ♪
♪ And I'm just tryna make it Tryna make it ♪
♪ 我只是试着去  试着去 ♪
♪ One more night One more night ♪
♪ 再熬过一夜  再过一夜 ♪
♪ I see the light ♪
♪ 我看到了光 ♪
Mom, you scared the shit out of me.
妈  你吓死我了
I thought somebody had broken into the house!
我还以为有人闯进了房子
What are you doing up so early?
你一大早在干什么
Today just seemed like the perfect day to see the sunrise.
今天看起来是看日出的好日子
Oh, and I may or may not have shat the bed.
我可能把床弄脏了  也可能没有
Let's get you cleaned up.
先来把你洗干净
Mom?
妈妈
- Hey. - Yeah?
-嘿  -怎么
Hey, I just wanted to let you know Mrs. Peters is here.
我只是告诉你彼得斯太太来了
Mrs. Peters, what the hell for?
彼得斯  她来干什么
It's your day off, Nora.
今天你休息  诺拉
It's fucking Sunday.
今天是他妈的星期天
I may be losing a lot of things, but my mind is not one of them.
我可能失去了很多  但我还没失去理智
Yes, you are of very sound mind, Mom.
是的  你很有理智  妈妈
That's right.
那当然
Are you feeling alright?
你感觉还好吗
Yeah, I'm great.
好  我很好
Well, I'm gonna take off to the gym, okay?
我要去训练馆了  好吗
Alright.
好吧
I'll be back later.
我一会儿回来
Knock yourself out.
你自便
Be nice to Mrs. Peters today, okay?
今天对彼得斯太太好点  好吗
No. I won't.
不  不可能
I bought milk. You ran out yesterday.
我买了牛奶  昨天就用完了
I'm sorry, I didn't think about it.
对不起  我没想到
I need milk for my tea.
我泡茶需要牛奶
I told you that when I agreed to watch over the house.
我答应照看房子的时候就告诉过你的
I'm sorry, I'll do better.
对不起  我会做得更好的
Please see that you do.
请务必做到
I ask so little.
我要求很少了
It's all knotted up.
都缠在一起了
Come on girl, keep breathing.
加油  姑娘  继续呼吸
Breathe through it! Alright, you guys do it.
呼吸  行了  你们来吧
You got like a sack of marbles in there, kid.
孩子  你里面很僵硬
You stretchin' at night?
你晚上有拉伸吗
You liar. You can't even fucking answer me right.
你撒谎  你他妈的都答不对
Alright, where's my rag doll?
好吧  我的布娃娃呢
Come on Nora, let's go, you gotta warm up Aisha. Let's go!
诺拉  去吧  你得给阿依莎热身  去吧
Let's go. You're on her. Get that choke out.
你被锁住了  要窒息了
What are you gonna do? Come on!
你打算怎么办  快啊
There you go.
好了
Now what are you gonna do if she tries to pass through?
现在如果她想过去你怎么办
Yeah, take the arm back!
对  把胳膊收回去
Look, you don't even need to use your hands!
听着  你甚至不需要用手
Side control!
侧向压制
Come on girl, take that.
来吧  姑娘  试下
Get the arm bar!
去锁臂
Alright, arm bars all day!
好的  锁牢了
Well actually, I can transition out of this.
事实上  我可以挣脱
Hey Nora, stop, watch the knee, come on!
诺拉  停  注意膝盖  快啊
Sorry.
对不起
Hey, shake it off.
嘿  停下来
Alright, well, let's... well that's enough of this shit.
好吧  我们  闹够了
Let's move on to something else. Aisha, come on. Let's go.
我们换个项目吧  阿依莎  走吧
Find me someone else please.
请给我另找个人
Hey! Yeah you. Come on.
你  过来
Hey, good job.
干得不错
I like what I'm seeing.
我喜欢这样的
Thanks.
谢谢
Here, here, here. Here.
这儿  这儿  这儿  这儿
Water.
水
Here, here.
这儿  这儿
Come here.
过来
Calm down, calm down.
冷静  冷静
I'm here, I'm here Mama. It's okay.
我在这里  妈妈  没事的
I'm always gonna be here.
我会一直在这里
Mom?
妈妈
I gotta take off to work. Are you feeling better?
我得去上班了  你感觉好些了吗
Fuckin' A.
真他妈
Mom, language, seriously.
妈  别说脏话  认真的
I thought we talked about the positivity thing.
我以为我们谈的是积极的方面
They're only words, Nora.
只是语言而已  诺拉
Like 73 across. The blank strikes back.
就像穿过73号  空挡反击
Positive energy and no cursing,
研究表明积极乐观不自怨自艾
research says is gonna help you clear out a lot of negativity.
会帮助你清除很多消极情绪
Given all my bad influence,
考虑到我的坏影响
how'd you end up such a Girl Scout?
你怎么会变成女童子军的
That's fucking true.
还他妈是真的
You're not funny.
一点也不好笑
You have a fucking good time.
你他妈的玩得很开心
I'll see you tonight.
今晚见
Thanks.
谢谢
How can I help you?
我能帮你什么忙吗
I called in an order to fill in my mom's prescription.
我电话订购了我妈妈的处方
It's under Catherine Poe.
凯瑟琳·坡名下
Catherine Poe?
凯瑟琳·坡
And you're Catherine Poe?
你是凯瑟琳·坡吗
Uh, no, that's my mother.
不  那是我妈妈
- You're not Catherine Poe? - No.
-你不是凯瑟琳·坡吗  -不是
Hold on.
等等
She's in here, but...
她名字在这里  但是
There's an error in my system, says no refills.
我的系统报错了  说不能再补充了
I can give you another refill but just as a one-time courtesy.
我可以再给你补充一次  但只此一次
Okay?
可以吗
Mhmm. Okay.
可以
- What? - Thank you.
-什么  -谢谢
That will be seventy dollars.
那要七十美元
Oh, no.
不是吧
Actually, my mom has Medicare so that shouldn't be any cost.
事实上  我妈妈有医保所以不应该收费
Okay.
好的
So it says here the classification for this drug has changed.
上面说这种药的分类已经改变了
Medicare only covers seventy-five percent. The rest is your copay.
医疗保险只报销75%  剩下的是你自费
So then the copay is the seventy dollars.
所以  自费70美元
The co-pay is the seventy dollars.
自费70美元
Well, I don't have seventy dollars.
我没有七十美元
Do you have a credit card?
你有信用卡吗
No.
没
- Debit card? - No, I don't have...
-借记卡  -不  我没有
We don't take checks.
我们不收支票
No, listen, you don't understand. I don't have seventy dollars.
不  听着  你不明白  我没有七十美元
This has always been free.
一直是免费的
You know I was never called about this or anything,
我没被人通知或者什么的
so I wasn't prepared to pay today, so I don't have seventy dollars.
所以我今天没准备付钱  我没有七十美元
I don't know what you want me to do, um...
我不知道你想让我怎么做
Look, the classification for the drug has changed.
听着  药物的分类已经改变了
There's really nothing I can do.
我真的没有办法帮你
Do you know what that medication is?
你知道那药是什么吗
You know what the-- what that does? What I need it for?
你知道那是什么吗  我需要它做什么吗
You're aware that my mom needs that medication, or she could die.
你知道我妈妈需要那种药  否则她会死的
Like you're aware of that, right?
你知道的  对吧
This has always been free. So I think there's just...
这一直是免费的  所以我觉得
I think you're doing something incorrect, and you need to fix it.
我认为你搞错了  你得纠正它
Okay. I've never had to pay for this.
好吗  我从来没有付过钱
You think I'm incorrect?
你觉得我弄错了
Yes, I do. I think you should look into your computer
是的  我觉得你应该看看你的电脑
and figure out a way to get my mother these drugs!
想办法给我妈弄到这些药
The way to get your mom these drugs is to give me seventy dollars.
给你妈妈这些药的方法是给我七十美元
This is fucking bullshit, can you go get somebody?
这他妈的胡扯  你能去找别人吗
Hey, hey doc. Hey doc, can I?
医生  医生  可以谈谈吗
Go get your manager. I gotta go to work.
去找你的经理  我得去上班了
So I need to fucking get outta here
所以我他妈的得离开这里
Doc, can I?
医生  我能
So please, can you give me my mom's medication.
拜托  能给我妈妈的药吗
Pharmacist? Can I talk to you for a second?
药剂师  我能和你谈一下吗
One second. Yeah, hold on.
等一下  好的  等一下
So I'll just take care of it if it's okay.
如果可以的话我来买单
What?
什么
I'll just take care of it if it's okay.
可以的话我来买单
We can just add it to my, to my stuff and we can handle it.
我们可以把它算到我的东西里  我们买单
What? This isn't a bar ,sir. What-- what are you saying?
什么  这不是酒吧  先生  你在说什么
I'll just take care of her stuff.
我会为她的东西买单
- Her stuff? - Yeah!
-她的东西  -是啊
You want to pay for this woman?
你想帮这个女人付钱吗
- Yeah. - Oh, no, I can't let you do that.
-是啊  -不  我不能让你这么做
No, it's no problem. Seriously, it's not a big deal.
不  没问题  说真的  没什么大不了的
No, like really.
不  真的
- No, I... - Look, I don't have money to pay you back.
-不  我   -听着  我没钱还你
Look it's up to you, I just...
随便你  我只是
My sister had cancer, so I understand what you're going through...
我姐姐得了癌症  所以我明白你的遭遇
and uh, yeah, I mean, I got it--
还有  我明白
You're a nice man.
你是个好人
Jason Wright. With a "W".
杰森·赖特  姓里有个"W"
- Right. - Right.
-对  -对
Okay. Lexapro, Risperdal...
好  依地普仑  利培酮
Yeah! Yes.
对
Thank you.
谢谢你
You're welcome.
不客气
It's early. I need some coffee.
还早呢  我要喝咖啡
You need some coffee? Wanna get some coffee?
你要咖啡吗  想来点咖啡吗
There's instant.
马上就好
You can just have it.
你可以取了
Thank you.
谢谢你
Have a good day. Have a better day. Yeah.
祝你今天顺心愉快
I have your drinks right here.
你们点的饮品  请在这取
Yo, I got this. Don't even mess with me.
我来付  不要和我客气
Okay.
随你
That'll be $11.50.
一共是11.5美元
Shit.
该死
So um... you said your-- your sister had cancer?
你是说  你的姐姐患了癌症吗
Yeah. Breast.
对  乳腺癌
Oh. What did you guys do?
那你们是怎么应对的呢
Did you guys just do like straight chemo?
你们是直接去化疗了吗
Did you try, like, the new drug trials, or...
还是去尝试了  新的药物测试什么的
The doctors kept misdiagnosing her.
医生之前一直误诊
I mean, like, when they found out what it actually was,
所以当他们查清我姐姐的病的时候
it was too late.
已经是晚期了
I'm...I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
Oh yeah, no. I mean, death is... death.
没事  死亡就是  死亡
But you can't-- you can't go backwards, right?
但是  你不能倒退  不是吗
You can't go backwards.
你不能回到以前
That's what all this--
我猜
I mean, I guess what some of these
这就是那些精神药物的
head drugs are for,
用处了
and I talk to the group. I go-- I go to this group.
我会去参加一些组织  聚会谈心
Very cool group meeting, super cool cats,
非常有意思  有超酷的猫
and we-- we watch movies and we read these books, and um.
我们还会一起看电影  看书什么的
Yo, you know, I know you're probably also
听着  我知道你
goin' through some, some heavy stuff,
也正在经历一些  难过的关
and I could totally introduce you to Pat.
所以我很想让你认识一下派特
Pat, she's my-- she's the group leader
派特  她是这个组织的头头
and she's a super cool chick.
而且她酷毙了
No, I'm good. Thank you, though, yeah.
谢谢你  但不用了
- Yeah? Right. - That's not--
-你不想吗  -这
No, I mean, no. I just was, was saying--
不是  你误会我了  我只是
Oh shit, I really gotta go, I'm sorry.
坏了  我现在得走了  抱歉
Look, this was all awesome,
这些都很好
and I really appreciate it, but I just--
我也很感激你  但我
But you, But you don't wanna talk to the--
但你不想和他们
you don't wanna talk to the crazy guy, right?
不想和那些疯狂的人谈心是吗
No!
当然不是
Like, my dad
像我爸爸
used to take a lot of the stuff that you were, um...
曾经也像你一样做这些事  但
Oh! Cool!
是吗  那很棒
I mean, not cool that your dad was
我的意思是  不是说你爸爸
like, I mean, like me, but it's just cool that--
像我一样去做这些就很棒  是说
Okay, I really have to go.
我真的得走了
I've gotta catch the 10:15 across town, so
我要赶上10点15的车到小镇的另一头去
sorry, but thank you!
抱歉  但谢谢你
Why, why're you cro--
你为什么要坐
the 10:15 across town,
坐那班车去那么远
why're you gonna do that?
为什么
Because it's the fastest way across town.
因为这是最快的办法了
Yo, why do guys always think that
为什么大家都自以为
they know the fastest way around?
他们知道最快的路呢
No! I'm-- I'm a driver!
不  我是  一名司机
Yeah! I have a perfect four star rating.
我有四星的高评价
I don't need a ride from you.
我不需要你载我
You've already done enough.
你已经帮我很多了
Seriously, I got you. You're not gonna make it.
说真的  我能帮你  你一个人不行的
You'll probably miss the bus, and uh,
你可能连公交车都赶不上
I'm a good driver. I can take you.
而且我是一名好司机  我可以带你去那里
So, what? Do I like, "app" you, or something?
所以呢  你是要我用"滴滴"下订单吗
No! I'm my own boss. Let's go.
不需要  我自己说了算  走吧
And I'm fast!
我开得很快
Safe! Safe and fast.
而且安全  又快又安全
Cool. Well, thank you.
我到了  谢谢你
This was-- you know your car is so nice.
你的车很舒适
- Yeah. - And it was very sweet of you.
-当然  -你也非常贴心
Yeah, thank you. This is something I do to meet people.
谢谢你夸我  这是我认识人的方式
They say it's good for you to talk to people
他们都说和别人谈心对我有益
'cause this stuff, uh--
因为我的心结
- Sure, Ok. - But you-- uh, the MMA.
-对  -但你  会综合格斗
MMA：综合格斗，即mixed martial arts
是一种规则极为开放的竞技格斗运动
Like, you straight roll with dudes?
你是直接和小伙子们打吗
Yeah, sometimes. Yeah.
对  有时候是
That's badass. That's badass.
那也太牛了  酷毙了
Yeah. I mean, sometimes it's actually better to fight with girls,
对  但是和女孩格斗更好
they put up more of a fight.
不像男孩子会不好意思下手
I'd like to-- I'd like to see that.
我很想  很想看一场格斗
I mean, do you-- at the gym do you guys have fights?
你们会在训练馆格斗吗
Like matches? Fi-- fighting matches?
比如格斗比赛  什么的
You like fights?
你喜欢格斗吗
I mean, me personally, I couldn't hurt a fly,
我  我连一只苍蝇都打不过
but I like, I mean I think I'd like to like, watch it.
比起自己上场  我更喜欢观看别人格斗
You know, 'cause it's-- the fighting,
你懂的  因为观看格斗比赛
to see the fighting is like, you know, it's like, cathartic!
就有一种  血脉偾张的感觉
Um, well, uh, my gym is hosting a tournament
我想想  我的训练馆在举办一场
in about two weeks.
为期大概两周的比赛
It's a female MMA tournament.
是女子综合格斗比赛
What? Like an all-girl blood sport?
真的吗  全女性吗
Like, straight Kumite style?
就像完全的对打风格吗
I don't know, I don't know what that means.
我不清楚  那是什么意思
Well, are-- are you gonna be in it?
那  你会参加吗
Am I gonna be in it?
你认真的吗
Uh, no! That's like, that's like a big-- no.
我当然不会参加  那可是一场大比赛
You, you should totally be in it.
你肯定得参加啊
I'm not like-- that's not. I just-- I just train.
不不不  我还只是个训练生
What? I mean, why not? You tol-- you totally should do it.
什么  为什么不去参加  你得上啊
I'm-- no. I'm not--
我  算了吧
I'm not that good. I'm not at that level, so, um...
我没那么优秀  还没到那个水平
But hey look, man, I really--
但听着  我真的
I have to get going.
我得走了
If you do wanna go see it,
如果你真的想看比赛
it's next week at the convention center.
下周会在会议中心举办
I'm there! I'm there. So there.
我会去的  我去定了
This is like the-- this is like the greatest thing
这是发生在我人生中
to happen to mankind, ever!
最棒的一件事了
Okay, cool. Bye, thank you.
那好  就这样吧  再见  谢谢你载我
Bye! We-- we should go.
再见  我们应该  一起去
I told you this bitch be hookin'.
我告诉过你这蠢女人会上钩的
Shit.
太神了
Like, we all tryna get money, but damn.
我们都想赚钱  但是
I mean, not-- not like that.
绝对不是那样赚的
I got you set up at one.
我把你安排在一点
You'll be in room 207 by then?
那时你应该打扫到207号房了对吧
Uh, yeah. Should be. Who is it?
对  应该是的  房主是谁
The fuck you care? Just do your thing.
管那么多干什么  你先管好你自己
Damn, girl! What'd that bag do to you?
姑娘  这沙包惹到你了吗
Shit! Champs aren't built overnight,
拜托  冠军可不是一蹴而就的
you know what I'm sayin'?
你明白吧
- You right. - You're not even sweating!
-我明白  -你汗都没流呢
I know. 'Cause I've been putting in that work.
我知道  因为我一直全力以赴锻炼
Six hours a day, that's what it does.
一天六个小时  会比你们轻松一些
Yeah, man. I just wanna get like you.
真好  我也想像你一样
- Then you better start training! - You're right.
-那你最好开始训练  -好的
- You're right. - Hustle up!
-知道了  -快点
Alright, see ya!
好了  过会见
What you lookin' at? C'mon!
你看什么呢  动起来
Let's see your stand up game!
让我看看你技术怎么样
Hands up.
双手就位
Alright, you gotta put your hips
你得把臀部也用上
into that shit, step into it.
集中力量
Okay.
好
Alright, chin down. A little lower.
下巴收起来一些
Keep the elbows tight.
保持肘部紧绷
No, don't spread like that! What the fuck?
要紧凑在一起  好好做
Breathe. Breathe! Let me hear you.
呼吸  让我听到你的呼吸声
Okay, it's not about hitting it so damn hard.
不是要你蛮力出拳
It's all technique.
注意技巧
Turn your hips.
带动臀部
Okay, a little more.
很好  再来
Longer extension.
伸展出去
Put your elbows in,
胳膊肘要带到位置
bring your elbows in. Okay.
带到位置  很好
You're puttin' in some work!
你打得越来越好了
Nora, Aisha, you're up!
诺拉  阿依莎  可以了
Let's work on some jiu-jitsu. Let's go, girls!
我们来练柔术  来吧  姑娘们
Thanks.
谢谢
What about the milk?
牛奶钱呢
Right.
不好意思
I don't need a babysitter, Nora.
诺拉  我不需要保姆
Thank you.
谢谢
Yes, you do, mom. You know I don't like to
不  妈妈  我工作的时候
leave you alone while I'm at work.
我不想只留你一人
She cheats at cards.
她玩牌耍赖
She cheats like a dirty fucking whore.
就像一个恶臭的婊子
Mom.
妈妈
- Yes. - Stop.
-怎么了  -别说了
Twenty dollars a day for what?
她啥也不干一天就能赚20块钱
To sit on her ass, cheating at cards
就是每天坐着  出老千
and taking long naps in the afternoon!
下午还一直睡觉
Mom!
妈妈
Look, just be glad it's not thirty dollars, okay?
你应该庆幸雇她不用30块
Eat your food, I'll be right back.
先吃饭吧  我马上回来
Chicken again.
又是鸡肉
Dammit, give me the money
该死  给我点钱
and maybe we can eat a decent meal!
也许我们能吃上一顿好的
The fuck?
我操
- She's in there again! - Are you fucking kidding me?
-她又来了  -你他妈在逗我吧
On a break! No, I'm dead serious!
在休息呢  不开玩笑  真来了
God damn, let's get this bitch out of here.
天呐  快把她赶走
Shit!
真晦气
It's like, is it possible?
你觉得这可能吗
She needs to go, she needs to go.
她必须滚蛋  就现在
You know, I'm tired of it, she needs to go.
我受够了  快让她滚
You need to go. Just like, honestly--
你真的得滚蛋了
What the fuck man? All day!
你什么毛病  一天都在休息
Breaks all day! Like, break queen.
请问您是偷懒女王吗
Can you do some work?
能请您去工作吗
- If you don't like it, you need - I was going to.
-要是你不想做  你可以  -我正准备去
- Really? - You're always on break!
-是吗  -可你一直在休息
If you don't wanna be here,
如果你不想待在这里
- just don't be here! - Get out.
-你可以滚  -滚蛋
- Hey! - Then just don't be here!
-停  -没人拦你
Hey, what's going on in here?
你们吵什么呢
She's not doing any fucking work!
她什么工作也不做
She's not working.
就在这里偷懒
- She's here, lounging and shit.- Are we the only
-她就会偷懒  -我们
maids you have here?
是这里唯一的女仆吗
Alright, look. I need the room
好了  听着  我要占用
for fifteen minutes. You two, out.
这个房间15分钟  你们俩  请出去
Nora, stick around.
诺拉  你留下
- So we don't get a break? - No break?
-所以我们连休息都不配吗  -不休息吗
- Come back in fifteen minutes. - In fifteen?
-15分钟就好  -是这样吗
That means in fifteen,
随你说
I can have fifteen plus fifteen,
我能再给你15分钟
and have a thirty minute break like Nora?
然后我们就可以像她一样休息30分钟吗
This is bullshit!
你就是在放屁
- Close the door! - Yeah. I'll close it.
-把门带上  -好  你说了算
You okay?
你还好吗
I know you've been going
我知道你最近
through a lot of stuff here lately.
有些难关要克服
I also have to say your work
但我也得说说你的工作状态
has been slipping a lot.
直线下降了
I'm sorry. I've just been a little tired.
很抱歉  我就是  有点累了
Tanya and Sasha giving you a hard time?
是因为塔尼娅和萨沙的排挤吗
Yeah, but don't worry.
有点  但别担心
It's nothing I can't handle.
我能应付一切
You stay away from those two.
你离她们远点
They are trouble.
她们是麻烦精
I try to. Every day.
我天天都是这么做的
Alright, let's go. Move your feet!
好  开始吧  注意走位
Hey, Nora lookin' pretty good.
诺拉  你表现很不错
Man! Great job, ladies!
做得好  姑娘们
That's what I'm talking about!
这就是我想看到的
Alright, good job, girls.
好了  你们做得很好
Yo! Nora! One o'clock.
诺拉  一点了
Fuck!
我操
What? He's gonna freak out if I don't pick up.
如果我再不接  他就要打爆我的电话了
Hey, babe, I'm training.
宝贝  我在训练呢
Can I call you back?
等会给你回电吧
Okay, okay. Talk to you later.
好  等会说
Yes, I'll call you back. Bye.
我会回电的  拜拜
There was a guy here looking for you today.
今天有个人来这里找你
Specifically you.
指定了找你
Uh, nice car. Big smile, teeth.
他开着一辆好车  露齿大笑
Well, if you see him again,
你要是再见到他
you call the cops. Alright?
直接报警  好吗
Trouble? No?
应该不是什么麻烦精吧
No. Just one more thing I have to fight.
不  只是另一件我要抗争的事
Be careful, Nora.
小心点  诺拉
C'mon! Move your feet, Nora!
快  双脚动起来  诺拉
Get your hands up, Aisha.
双手举起来  阿依莎
That's it, that's it! C'mon, girls, work!
这就对了  姑娘们  动起来
We got five days till
我们距离
Double A Double A Tournament, let's go!
双打比赛只有五天了  加油
C'mon!
给我加油
Quit pissin' around! Let's go!
别胡闹了  使出力气
You got this, girl.
你能赢  姐妹
She's ready for this thing, man.
那比赛她已经稳了
- She's got something goin' for her. - Nice.
-她要出招了  -妙极了
- Okay! - I'm surprised, dude.
-上啊  -兄弟  我被惊到了
Okay. Okay, rookie! Go ahead!
快  菜鸟  继续打呀
Pay attention! Get your hands up!
集中注意  重拳出击
That's it, that's it!
对了  就是这样
Watch it! Oh.
注意  小心
Okay, that's it, that's it.
结束了  别打了
Yup. Back to the drawing board.
还得从头再来
Nora, you good?
诺拉  你还好吗
Nah, it's all good. We were sparring, and I just got distracted.
我没事  实战的时候我分神了
Damn! It's still bleeding?
我去  还在流血吗
Yeah, I think so. Yeah, it's not stopping.
是啊  好像止不住了
Here.
我看看
Oh, no. Aisha, you don't have to do that.
阿依莎  不用  你不用帮我
I know. But I am.
不行
Lean back. Lean back.
抬头  抬头
Does that hurt?
疼吗
Ow!
疼
You're such a little bitch.
你这个小婊子
Shut up! To you, maybe.
闭嘴  也许我只对你婊
Okay. I'm gonna try one more thing.
我得再检查一下
I just want to make sure it's not broken.
想确定看看骨头断没断
- Does that hurt? - No.
-这样疼吗  -不疼
Is this your first time?
这是第一次被撂倒吗
No.
不是
You've been knocked out before?
你以前也被打倒过
Gotten beat up before?
以前被打过吗
Uh, no-- yeah.
不  有过
Gonna be a nice one.
过两天还是个漂亮鼻子
I'm sorry. I thought that's what you wanted.
对不起  我以为你也对我有意思
Hey, look. I'm really sorry.
真的  我真的很抱歉
I didn't mean to cross the line.
我不是想越界
Look, I want you to know I respect you, wholeheartedly,
你要知道我很尊重你  打心眼里尊重你
and I'm so appreciative for everything you guys have done for me.
我很感激你们为我所做的一切
You guys?
我们
Yeah! You, and Rosheen and the gym.
是啊  你  罗辛  还有这个训练馆
So you just go and make out with everybody?
所以你是随便跟人上床吗
No!
当然不是
I'm lookin' out for you 'cause you're my sparring partner.
我关心你  是因为你是我的训练搭档
For now.
目前是而已
'Cause I'm training with you. That's it.
我在和你搭档训练  就这么简单
I just misread things, that's all.
是我会错意了  就这样
So you just kiss people who are married?
所以你乱亲已经结婚的人吗
Well, are you happy?
那你快乐吗
With your marriage?
你的婚姻幸福吗
Get outta my face, Nora.
从我面前滚开  诺拉
I'm sorry, Aisha.
对不起  阿依莎
What is a ten letter word for mayonnaise?
蛋黄酱是由十个字母组成的吗
'Cause I think it's fucking mayonnaise.
我觉得这个应该是填蛋黄酱
What other-- what other word could that be?
不然还会是哪个单词
- I think it's a trick. - Hey, I'm going for my run.
-这应该是个陷阱  -我要去跑步了
You gonna be okay?
你在家可以吗
Yeah, yeah. No, no, no. You go for your run.
当然可以  我自己来  你去跑步吧
I would go with you, except for this whole, shitty dying thing.
要不是我快死了  我也想和你一起去
You know, it's not funny, mom.
一点都不好笑  妈妈
I can't tell if you're being sarcastic or not.
我不知道你是不是在说反话
I get it. Who wants to sit around watching me fall apart anymore?
我懂的  没人愿意坐在这儿看我自暴自弃
So you run, it's fine.
你去跑步吧  没事的
Look, you know that I'm training right now.
你知道我最近在训练呢
For what? Wrestling?
训练啥  摔跤吗
It's not just wrestling. I'm actually getting pretty good at this.
这不只是摔跤  我在这方面真的很有天赋
Okay. So where's that lead?
好吧  这对你将来有什么好处
A career? I don't know.
或许成为职业选手呢  我也不知道
Some people actually make really good money at this.
有人真的可以以此为生  衣食无忧
Okay, but really good people, right?
也是  但只有佼佼者才能做到  对吧
I am good.
我就是佼佼者
Your face, Nora.
诺拉  你脸上的神情
Is that a sign that you're good?
是佼佼者应该有的吗
Well, actually, there are a few people at the gym who think
实际上训练馆有不少人觉得
that I should join the upcoming MMA tournament, so yeah.
我应该去参加即将举行的MMA锦标赛
So I am.
所以  我很强
MMA. Is that mixed martial anaconda?
MMA  指的是混合蟒蛇武打
Masculine marshmallow Abercrombie?
棉花糖硬汉阿伯克龙比
Motherfuckin' manly assholes?
还是  欠操的王八蛋
Look, I'm gonna go for my jog. Are you gonna be alright?
听着  我要去跑步了  你自己在家行吗
Yeah, I will be. Will you?
当然  你一个人行吗
Yo, yo, yo, Nora! One o'clock?
诺拉  一点行吗
Not today, man.
今天不行
Man, I told you that boxing shit is no good for business.
我告诉过你  打拳挣不了什么钱
I mean, maybe some dude's into that black eye stuff,
也许有人就喜欢被揍的感觉
but come on man, look at you.
自己照照镜子看看
You're all jacked up and swolled up like a dude.
全是伤  人都肿了  跟个男人一样
Well, I gotta lay off anyways. I got a fight this weekend.
随便吧  我要休息  我上周末打了一场
No, no, no, no, no. This shit messes me up, man!
不行  一堆破事已经够让我烦的了
- Look - What am I supposed to tell this guy?
-听着  -我该给这家伙说什么
I don't know! Tell him I have a blistering STD or some shit.
我不知道  就说我突然得了性病  随便编
Fuck, man!
操
Aight.
好吧
Alright, one week, okay?
歇一周  行吧
One week, and then we back to business as usual.
一周之后照常上班
Look, Jesus.
听着  黑修斯
I been thinking and, and-- don't take this the wrong way.
我一直在想  你别误会
It's just, um,
这真的
I'm not real sure I wanna keep doing this.
我不确定我是不是还想干这个
The fuck you talking about?
你他妈说的什么屁话
We got a deal here. A good deal! You making
我们说好的  这还是你定的
change, ain't you?
你现在想反悔吗
Yeah. But how much change are you making on this?
是啊  可你也没按我们说好的来啊
I get my share! I set this shit up, I keep it goin'--
这是我应得的  我安排好  让一切照常
I'm the one who watches your ass when you conductin' business,
是我在你干那档子事时帮你盯梢的
so fuck yeah, I'm gonna get my share!
所以怎样  我拿走了我应得的
I gotta eat too, right? What am I supposed to do?
我也要吃饭啊  不然我咋办
Alright, I'm gonna get you ten more a pop, okay?
算了  我再多给你加十块  行吧
Ten more a pop, and that's it.
再加十块  不说了
Any more than that, these dudes can go downtown
再加钱  有的哥们用这个价可以去市中心
and get club pussy for that price.
找个俱乐部小姐玩了
Alright, Jesus.
行了  黑修斯
Think whatever you want, alright,
随便你怎么想  好吧
but nobody wants your ass that bad.
但真没什么人想要操你
Then you know what, Jesus?
你知道吗  黑修斯
Ain't nobody gonna get me then, how 'bout that?
以后也没人可以操到我  你说呢
Fuck!
我操
I know what you be doin'.
我知道你都干了什么
You don't know shit.
你知道个屁
Oh, I know.
我当然知道
You think that nobody's gonna find out
你以为没人知道
what the fuck you doin' around here?
你在这偷偷摸摸干什么吗
Shit, Jesus tried to get me to do that same shit.
黑修斯想让我也干这个
And I was like, "Nah, fuck that!" No, bitch.
我操  我跟他说没可能
Don't look at me like that, like I couldn't. Like you.
贱人别这么看我  我可没你这么贱干这个
Why can't you just leave me alone?
你就不能让我一个人待一会吗
Because I don't fuckin' like you. You're entitled.
不能  我他妈烦死你了  你整天牛逼哄哄
You're mean. You walk around here like you own this shit.
自私自利  感觉好像这地方是你家一样
You don't own no-- the fuckin' hotel!
这旅馆才不是你的地盘
You're not nice. You're a bitch!
你很讨人厌  你很贱
- I'm a bitch? - You a bitch.
-我贱吗  -你贱
Is there like, a fake mirror here
你是不知道自己几斤几两吗
or something? 'Cause you're the bitch!
你才下贱  照照镜子吧你
A fake mirror? Bitch, I know I'm a bitch!
要我照镜子  婊子  我知道我贱
I just letting you know that you are a bitch.
我就想告诉你  你也好不到哪儿去
- Okay? Sitting on the steps. - Well, I don't give
-知道不  还坐在台阶上  -好吧  我他妈
a shit what you don't like.
才不管你讨厌什么
Oh! You gettin' tough now?
发飙了吗
You tough? You 'bout to do somethin'?
你要发飙了吗  要揍我吗
I'm guessin' that you got somethin' coming to you.
你绝逼摊上事儿了
Let's go.
打一架吗
You think I'm finna fight you right now at my job?
你以为我要在上班时候跟你打架吗
Why not?
干吗不打
Um, real adults in real life actually
现实生活告诉我们真正的成年人
care about getting paid for shit.
只关心的是挣多少钱
All of us can't fuck for work and for money.
没人会搞砸自己的工作搞得自己挣不了钱
So I need this job.
我还得上班呢
So, it's not gon' be today, not here, but it's comin' to you.
你现在没事  你很快就会摊上事的
'Cause you fuckin' deserve it.
你他妈活该
Walkin' around here like your shift don't stink.
别四处晃荡讨人嫌
You ain't nothin', bitch.
你屁都不是  你个贱人
You just like the rest of us bitches,
你和我们没什么区别  干的都是下贱活儿
walkin' around here, cleaning rooms.
挨个房间去打扫
Get that through your skull, how 'bout that? Fuckin' psycho.
记着这一点  知道不  神经病
Lazy as shit Nora.
懒得像屎一样  诺拉
Go ahead, drink your soda.
继续吧  喝你的苏打
I plan on it.
喝着呢
Got nothin' to be done around here, right?
没你的活儿是吧
I'm on my break, I don't know about you.
这是我的休息时间  谁管你
Yeah.
可不是呢
Wish we all had a break like you.
谁都想像你这样休息
Alright, guys, get in here. Keep those hands up.
伙计们  投入一点  手举高
Give 'em another twenty, coach.
教练  再给他们加二十组
I got a waiver request for you to enter the tournament.
我收到了弃权申请  所以你去参加比赛吗
Is that right? You entered?
是吗  你要参加吗
Yeah.
是
Alright.
行吧
Why not?
随便你
Where's my mother?
我妈呢
Oh, hey.
回来了
Hello.
是啊
See you tomorrow.
明天见
Oh! Mrs. Peters?
彼得斯太太
Yes?
怎么了
Um, I'm not gonna have the money to pay for the next few days.
我这几天可能没法给你日结了
Would it be okay if I just paid you in full next week?
下周一次性结清行吗
That's not our arrangement.
这可和当初约定的不一样
I know, um, I was kinda hopin' you'd help me out
我知道  我希望你能理解一下
and it'd be like a one-time thing.
仅此一次而已
The reason arrangements are made is so that
当初我们之所以约定好就是为了双方
all the parties involved know what's expected of them.
都能清楚自己的权利和义务
- I know, I just thought that may - Jesus Christ, Mary!
-我知道  我只是想  -我的个老天  玛丽
If she says she's gonna pay you next week,
她说了下周给你付钱
she'll pay you next week!
那她肯定给你
Don't be such a fucking dickweed!
别这么操蛋行吗
I'll see you tomorrow.
明天见
- Oh, and Mrs. Peters? - Yes?
-彼得斯太太  -什么事
I also have something this Saturday night.
我周六晚上有点事
Again, not agreed to!
又来  我不同意
I know, but it's just a one-time thing.
我知道  就这一次
Double.
两倍工钱
Oh, jump in front of a fucking truck, Mary.
你他妈的在碰瓷吧  玛丽
That's fine! Double, that's totally fine.
没问题  两倍就两倍
Thank you, Mrs. Peters. Thank you.
谢谢你  彼得斯太太
Oh, she is such a bitch!
这个婊子太贱了
Too much. Stop it with all that.
够了  别再说了
No! She is messing with my positive healing energy.
我不  她扰乱了我积极向上的正能量
You know, if you're going to play cards with the terminally ill,
要知道如果你和绝症病人打牌
you should at least lose a few hands. It's only polite.
你至少输几把  这是礼貌
Just 'cause you suck at cards, mom,
妈  你玩牌很烂
doesn't mean that she's a cheater.
不代表人家出千了
She has no fucking class.
她牌技也不咋地
Aw, I used to be strong.
我过去也很强壮
I used to have boobs.
我也有胸
This shit just eats everything.
现在屁都没了
Nora, tell me...
诺拉  告诉我
What are your odds in this thing?
你胜算有多大
'Cause, you know, it'll be weird
要知道  我的意思是  如果你比我
if you die before I do. That's all I'm sayin'.
先死的话  就太不合理了
Mom, I'm fighting for you.
妈妈  我是在为你而战
You know, this is a lot of money.
赢了会有一大笔钱的
Honey, don't fight for me.
宝贝  不要为我
Fight for you.
为你自己而战
This is stage four.
这病已经发展到第四阶段了
Stage four of fucking four.
他妈的第四阶段啊
Yeah, well, you'll thank me when you overcome the odds.
等你战胜疾病的时候  你会感谢我的
Oh, I won't be here to thank anyone.
我谁都不谢
And then what are you gonna do? Hm?
那你到时候准备做什么
Mom--
妈妈
Look, Nora, I'm gonna die
听着  诺拉  我快死了
and it'll probably be in the next two months.
也许活不过两个月了
And you need a realistic plan.
你得制定个现实点的计划
I'm not listening to this shit.
我不听你在这胡说八道
You will lose this house without my disability
我死了之后你会失去这座房子
then where are you gonna go?
到那时你要去哪呢
What are you gonna do?
做什么呢
I have a plan.
我有计划
I'm gonna win this tournament, I'm gonna win the money,
我要赢下这场比赛  把钱拿到手
and I'm gonna get you the proper care that you need!
然后带你去接受合适的治疗
Oh, honey, that's not real.
亲爱的  这计划不现实
That's just a dream.
只能算是个梦罢了
Well, it's my dream. Stop trying to take it away from me.
那也是我的梦  别想把它从我身边夺走
Hey! Nora!
嘿  诺拉
Yo! Hey, it's me! It-- It's Jason!
是我  是杰森
Oh, hey, what's up, Jason? Yeah, I gotta go to work.
你好啊  杰森  那个  我得去上班了
No, hey, wait! Wait one second, though!
那个  等一下  就一会
What do you want, man?
兄弟  有什么事吗
Um, i--
我
Look, I already thanked you
听着  我很感激
for helping with my mom's medication.
你替我付钱买了我妈妈要用的药
I really have nothing else I can give you.
但我实在是没有什么可以报答你的
I just--
只是
I just can't stop thinking about you.
只是你在我脑海里挥之不去
But-- I mean, not--
但  我是说  不是
I mean, not in like in some crazy person way.
不是像有些傻逼一样
Some like, some guy who just
像一些  一些不速之客
just shows up at your work unannounced.
突然出现在你工作的地方
No, not like that guy
我  我跟他们不一样
but more like the guy who
我更像是一个
is well-balanced on his meds and he just really thinks
精神正常的人  是发自内心地觉得
that you're this super cool chick and would love to get a chance
你是一个非常酷的女孩子
to get to know you better kind of way.
想进一步了解你而已
Look, I'm sorry. You seem nice.
听着  我很抱歉  你看上去人不错
That doesn't mean I owe you anything.
但我不欠你什么
I shoulda wore the V-neck!
我应该穿V领衬衫来的
I should've worn the V-neck.
真该穿那件V领衬衫来
I--
操
You know, it could've-- coulda gone worse. Coulda gone worse.
没关系  还可以  表现得还可以
Aight, give me another week, alright? I--
好  再给我一周  可以吗  我
Alright. Alright, man, don't be a tough guy, alright?
好的好的  兄弟冷静一下好吗
Do you-- If you-- Alright.
你  如果你  好吧
Okay, you're right, you got it.
好吧  没错  会给你安排的
Yes, sir! Anytime, after 3 PM, check-in!
没错  下午三点之后的任何时间均可入住
Very good, uh, just stop by and we can accommodate.
非常好  直接过来  我们会为您安排食宿
Very good. Thanks.
好的  谢谢您
Uh, Mr. Burns?
伯恩斯先生
Ah, Nora! Um, what can I do for you?
诺拉  有什么事吗
Oh. More problems with Sasha? Have a seat.
跟萨沙又起冲突了吗  请坐
No. Um, I actually need to ask for Saturday off.
不  那个  我想在周六请天假
Satur--
星  星期
This Saturday?
这周星期六
Yeah
没错
Saturday, you know, is our busiest day of the week.
你也知道星期六是咱们这最忙的一天
Is it-- Is it that important to you?
那事对你很重要吗
- Yeah, it really is. - Aw, you're killin' me here.
-对  挺重要的  -你让我很难办啊
You're killin' me, Nora! You--
诺拉  真难办啊  你
Saturday we're gonna be especially busy.
这周六会特别忙
Um. I will think about it, okay? I will--
让我考虑一下  好吗  我会
I don't know if I can deal with this now.
我不知道现在能不能给你答复
I'll think about it. I'll, I'll let you know.
我想一想  我会  会给你答复的
Mr. Burns, I never ask for time off.
伯恩斯先生  我从未请过假
I know that, I know that.
我知道  我知道
But you're my best girl. I-- What am I gonna do?
但你是我这最好的员工  我还能怎么办
I'm here for you all the time! All I'm asking is for one day.
我一直在给你干活  我只想要一天的假期
Saturday.
星期六
Yes.
对
It's gonna be really busy Saturday.
看来这周六一定会很忙
Thank you, Mr. Burns.
谢谢你  伯恩斯先生
Hey-- you owe me!
你欠我一次
Eh, apparently I owe everyone.
好吧  显然我现在谁都欠
Who was the suit?
那个穿衬衫的是谁
What are you talking about?
你在说什么
Mr. GQ in the grey beamer!
灰宝马车里那个时尚先生
What, you back-doorin' me, Nora?
啥  你在跟我耍心眼吗  诺拉
No!
没有
Then who's the fuckin' suit?
那他妈那个衬衫男是谁
He's just some guy I met!
他就是一个我前几天遇到的路人
Some guy, my ass!
一个路人  我的天啊
What? You think you can cut out the middle man?
什么  你觉得你能把中间人排除在外
Huh? Start your own lil' business?
自立门户  是吗
Nah, you wanna deal, you deal through me.
不行  你想卖  你也得通过我去卖
I'm not dealing! He's just some guy I met!
我没有卖  他只是个我见过的路人
You just met some rich ass guy, right?
你刚刚遇见一个富佬  是吗
If you're gonna lie, at least make it convincing.
撒谎至少也装得像一点啊
What is that supposed to mean?
你这话什么意思
No suit goes bottom trollin'!
你以为凯子那么好钓吗
I catch you fuckin' around my back again
再他妈背着我搞小动作
I'm gonna mess you up, Nora.
我就搞死你  诺拉
Yo, you don't own me, alright? Why don't you back up?
你管不到我  懂吗  你离我远点行吗
The fuck you doin'?
你他妈干什么
You fuckin' crazy, huh? Fucking crazy?
你他妈疯了是吗  想造反是吗
- Are they fighting? - Oh yeah, they are.
-他们在打架吗  -天啊  还真的
- Oh, shit! Oh, shit! Oh shit! - What the fuck?
-我操  我操  这他妈的  -什么鬼
Oh my god! Hit back, Jesus! You look stupid!
我操  还手啊  黑修斯  你跟个傻逼一样
- You're gettin' your ass beat! - Enough!
-你被打的真惨  -别打了
You a pussy, Jesus, that's crazy.
你个怂逼  黑修斯  真是疯了
She just molly wopped you.
她都骑你脸上了
He didn't do nothin', he just stood there!
他啥也没干  就在那挨打
Yeah, you got fucked up.
是啊  你被揍惨了
Fuck y'all!
去你们妈的
Got your ass kicked!
被揍惨了吧
I didn't get my ass kicked!
我没被揍惨
Fuck you-- oh shit!
滚你妈的  我操
- Oh shit! - Oh! Oh shit!
-我操  -我的天
Nope! Nope, you're dead. He's fucked up.
不  不  你要死了  他完蛋了
You're gonna die, you can't breathe. Damn!
你要死了  没法呼吸了都  兄弟
Better stand up, Jesus! Stand up!
你最好反抗一下  黑修斯  起来啊
What the hell is go-- What is going on here?
这他妈怎么  这怎么回事
Get her off me!
让她离我远点
Jesus, stop it, and you get off of her right now!
黑修斯  停手  你给我从她身上下来
I'm ch-- me? She's cho--!
我  我吗  她在锁
Get-- Break it up, you two!
给我  给我分开  你俩
C'mon! Behave like humans, for crying out loud!
快点  都正常点  我的天啊
Jesus! In my office, right now!
黑修斯  来我办公室  马上
Man, fuck her!
去她妈的
I said now! Get the hell in my office!
现在  快给我滚去办公室
And you two!
还有你俩
Sasha, mind your own business! Get--
萨沙  这不关你的事  给我
No. No! This is my business, Mr. Burns!
不  不  这就是我的事  伯恩斯先生
You know, you-- you're always playing favorites!
你知道吗  你总是对她偏心
And you know, your favorite has been fuckin' Johns in these rooms
但你知道吗  你的小宝贝就在这几间房里
night after night for months right under your nose!
夜以继日地在你眼皮底下操着男人
That's right.
没错
- How you feel about that? - You're welcome, we told you.
-现在感觉如何  -别客气  我们告诉你了
Nora, is this true?
诺拉  是真的吗
Nora, I'm talking to you.
诺拉  我问你话呢
Just tell me it is not true.
告诉我这不是真的
Oh, God.
天呐
Yep. Boom.
完了  完了哦
You two, get back to work. Get-- go!
你俩  回去工作  给我滚
You just-- you just-
你这人  你只是
Got the truth now.
现在知道了吧
You're welcome.
别客气哦
I give you every break in the book
该休息的我都让你休息了
and this is what you do to me?
然后你就这么对我吗
Forget the Johns, you fucked me!
别管那些嫖客了  你真伤我心
I thought you were better than that.
我本来以为你还不至于堕落至此
Just get your shit and go. You do not work here anymore.
收拾好东西走吧  你被开除了
Get your hands up, Nora! C'mon! C'mon!
把手抬起来  诺拉  加油  加油啊
- Come here! - Keep moving, keep moving!
-打我啊  -保持步伐  保持移动
What the hell?
怎么回事
Why'd you enter the tournament if you're just gonna stand there?
你光站那挨打怎么参加比赛
The fuck is your problem, Nora?
你他妈怎么回事  诺拉
I don't have a problem!
我没事
What do you mean you don't have a fuckin' problem?
你说你没事  你他妈什么意思
You got a big ass problem!
我看你他妈有一堆破事
Come on!
打起精神
You entered the competition and you can't even beat Rosheen!
你连罗辛都打不过  还打什么比赛啊
Oh, co-- What?
天啊  你说啥
You don't have to fight in this fuckin' competition!
你不想打就别他妈参赛了
I don't fuckin' have a choice. I don't fucking have a choice!
我他妈别无选择了懂吗  别无选择了
Are you girls gonna fight or Nora, you need me to string you up
诺拉你到底要不要打  还是你想
and let everyone use you as a punching bag? Come on!
让我把你吊起来给别人当沙袋打  振作点
- I am fighting! - No, you're fuckin' not!
-我在打了  -你他妈在打个鬼
Then fight, Nora! Fuckin' fight! Fight! Fight, Nora!
你跟我打啊  诺拉  出手啊  打啊  打啊
Come on.
注意点
Alright, that's enough!
好了  别打了
Fuckin' fight!
你他妈打啊
That's enough! Let it go! Get up! Get up! Get up!
够了够了  别打了  起来起来起来
- Fuckin' fight! - Come on.
-你他妈打啊  -够了
- Come on, let it go! - Fuckin' fight!
-够了够了  冷静点  -你他妈打啊
- She ain't doin' shit! - Take a fuckin' walk!
-她什么也不干  -给我去走一圈
She's not fuckin' doin' shit!
她他妈什么也不做
This is the tournament!
就他妈快比赛了
- Get your ass out and take a walk! - Yes!it is!
-给我出去冷静冷静  -对啊都快比赛了
Get up.
起来
No, no, no. Get in here. The fuck's goin' on with you?
不不不  你进来  你他妈怎么回事
Nothing. I'm fine.
没事  我挺好的
Get it together.
振作起来
Aight?
好吗
I'm sorry, Aisha.
对不起  阿依莎
I didn't mean to mess up your training.
我不是故意搞砸你训练的
It's just I'm messing everything up nowadays.
我只是最近什么都搞砸了
Stop feeling sorry for yourself
别再自怨自艾了
and fight for what the fuck you really want.
想要什么就他妈去奋斗
Yeah, I don't know what I want anymore.
可是我现在不知道我到底想要什么了
Mom?
妈
Mrs. Peters, were you sleeping?
彼得斯太太  你是在睡觉吗
Is that my mom coughing?
你听见我妈在咳嗽了吗
You're supposed to be watching her!
你本来应该去照看她的
Jesus!
天啊
Mom. Hey! Mom!
妈妈  妈妈
Mom, wake up. Mom. You okay?
妈妈  醒醒  你还好吗
No, no, I'm okay.
没事  没事  我挺好的
This is normal, everyday death spiral shit.
很正常  不就是每天都觉得我快死了
You're okay?
你真没事吗
Yeah, I'm okay.
是的  没事
Alright, 'cause I brought you dinner.
好吧  我给你带晚饭了
Oh! Let me guess, chicken!
让我猜猜  还是鸡肉
No, I brought you hamburgers
不对  我给你带了
because I know they're your favorite.
你最喜欢吃的汉堡
Aw, that they are. Thank you.
确实是我最喜欢的  谢谢你
You're welcome.
不客气
Spit it out.
说吧
I got fired today.
我今天被开除了
For what?
为什么
For fighting.
因为打架
Fighting at work.
工作的时候打架
It wasn't my fault.
不是我的错
You know, I just was standing up for myself
我只是在维护自己
and it got a little physical,
只是稍微起了点肢体冲突
that's all.
就这样
Well, that must have been a dandy of a brouhaha.
那你打的一定是个烦人的自恋狂吧
Look, Mom.
听着  妈妈
I don't know how I'm gonna pay for everything without this job.
没了这工作我不知道要怎么满足日常开销
I don't even know how I'm gonna pay Mary back!
我都不知道怎么给玛丽工资
Oh, fuck that cow.
哎哟  去她妈的吧
What is she gonna do to you, sue ya?
她能拿你怎么办  起诉你吗
For what? This shithole?
为了什么  就这破地
No. You will find something else, Nora.
听着  你还会找到其他工作的  诺拉
I just want better for us.
我只想让咱俩过得更好
Well then,
那好吧
I guess there's only one thing you can do.
我想你现在只剩一个选项了
Win that damn tournament.
拿下比赛
Win that whole goddamn MM-- Mountain Man Asshole thing.
把那该死的综合什么什么玩意赢下来
You go kick everybody's goddamn ass.
去把她们打得落花流水
Hey, Nora. I have your, uh, severance check here.
诺拉  这是你的遣散费
Cool.
好
You're pissed at me, huh?
你一定恨透我了  对吧
I coulda called the law on you,
本来我可以去报案的
you'd been in jail. You know that?
那你就得去蹲局子了  知道吗
As it is, Jesus is probably gonna press charges.
现在看来  黑修斯很可能会去起诉你
Jesus is not gonna call the cops.
黑修斯才不会去报警
Yeah, maybe.
也许会  也许不会
But you just can't beat the hell out of a coworker.
但你和同事打架一定是错的
It's never the answer.
解决不了问题
Well, you don't know how far I was pushed.
你想象不到我已经被逼得走投无路了
I can guess.
我想我知道
Hurting somebody just 'cause you think you're right?
因为你觉得自己是对的  就有理由打人吗
That is a fast track to a criminal record, kid.
简直就是坐上了牢房直通车  孩子
Yeah, well, that'd just be one more
真好  生活中不止奋斗[打架]
bullshit thing that I have to fight.
现在还得多听你几句屁话
Why?
为什么
Why does it always have to be a fight with you, Nora?
所有的事情到你这  就要打架解决  诺拉
Because everything is a fight, Billy!
因为一切都要靠奋斗[打架]  比利
Yes, yes, you keep telling me.
对  对  你一直就这么说的
I question your definition of "fight"!
简直不懂你对这两个字的定义
Rotate that hip. C'mon.
转动臀部  拜托
Alright, good job girls. That's the day.
好  表现不错  姑娘们  今天就到这儿吧
- Thank you, Coach! - Yep.
-谢谢教练  -不客气
Aisha, Nora! You're up!
阿依莎  诺拉  轮到你俩上了
Thanks.
谢谢
Alright ladies, it's game time.
好了  姑娘们  游戏时间到了
Two o'clock tomorrow evenin',
明天下午两点
I'll meet you both at the Civic Center and
我在文娱中心等你们俩
we'll see what we see.
到时候一切见分晓
But for right now, however,
但就目前来说
I need you to really concentrate on
你们给我打起万分精神
your structure and your footwork.
投入到自己的动作和步法中去
Tonight, get your rest.
今晚  就好好休息
Eight hours at least, please.
至少都要睡够八小时
Maybe more, if you can.
如果想的话  也可以多睡会
And then, maybe a light run in the morning,
然后  早上可以去跑一跑
a nap, and then it's show time.
小憩一下  然后就该你们展现自我了
You girls got any questions?
还有什么问题吗
- No, Coach. - Alright. Take it easy.
-没有  教练  -好的  放松点
- Hey, Aisha? - Sup?
-嘿  阿依莎  -怎么
Just wanted to say I'm really sorry about yesterday.
我想说  昨天的事我真的很抱歉
Nah, you're good. I was a little too hard on you.
不  你没错  是我有点太过分了
Nah, it was good.
不  我说真的
You really showed me what it is I want.
因为你  我总算意识到我想要什么
And what's that, huh? Huh? Huh?
那你说说  你想要什么
I wanna win this.
我想要赢
You know you're gonna have to get through me, right?
那你也知道  拳场上你得先打赢我  对吧
I'm not your damn sidekick, boo!
我们又不是合作取胜
Yeah, I know.
对  我知道
Maybe it's you who's gonna have to get through me!
但谁打得赢谁还说不定呢
Alright, honey.
好啊  亲爱的
Oh, hey! Save the full contact for the tournament!
干嘛呢  把实力都留到锦标赛上去好吗
That was my bad, Coach.
对不起  教练  我的错
Apparently, I'm really bad at reading signals.
事实证明  我不擅长看对手的进攻信号
Yeah, well, bromancing her to death isn't working.
是的  但也没必要把她往死里揍
Keep moving!
继续练习
There you go.
开始吧
Nora! Where you at?
诺拉  你在哪呢
Over here, Coach!
我在这儿  教练
Hey, good job today, kid.
今天表现不错  孩子
Thanks.
谢谢
I feel like your headspace is finally getting dialed in.
感觉你终于开窍了  如鱼得水
That's what you need, alright?
你需要的就是保持好这种状态
Now, I want you to go home tonight, get plenty of rest,
好了 今晚回家以后  好好休息
load up on carbs, and get a lot of sleep. Alright?
多吃点碳水化合物  多睡一会儿  好吗
And please get that damn hair braided.
然后拜托你把这头头发编成辫子
I was just gonna like, put it in like a bun or something.
我原本就想把它随便弄一下  做个发髻
No you're not. I got you covered, they're expecting you.
别那样弄  我和他们说好了  直接去就行
- Tonight? - Yep.
-今晚吗  -对
Rosheen, I don't have money to pay for this.
罗辛  我付不起这个钱
I got ya. It's taken care of, don't worry about it.
没事  不要操心钱的事  我已经搞定了
Really?
真的吗
Thank you.
谢谢您
Alright. My little rag doll won't be so raggy!
当然  不能让我的布娃娃蓬头垢面就上场
Go get 'em, girl!
快去吧  孩子
Hi. Can I help you?
你好  需要做头发吗
Um, Rosheen sent me to get my hair done for my fight.
罗辛让我来  为我明天的比赛做头发
Like, braids or something?
比如  弄成辫子或者其他的什么
Yeah, yeah. I know. I can get you for two hundred dollars.
我知道了  那我只收你两百美元
Oh. Rosheen said that it was "taken care of?"
可罗辛说的是  "已经和你们说好了"
What do you think this is?
你觉得我们这儿是什么店
A charity for some straggedy-ass white girl?
给邋遢的白人女孩免费做头发的慈善机构
I'm sorry there must have been some misunderstanding.
抱歉  可能是有什么误会
I'm sorry.
非常抱歉
Oh, no, no, no, no, come back, come back!
哦  不  不  不  不  回来回来
I'm just teasing you! Come on, I'm playing!
刚刚是在逗你玩  好吧  开玩笑的
Come on in. Now, damn!
快回来  现如今  大家也真是的
Don't take everything so damn personal! Come on!
觉得所有人都是在针对自己  快来吧
It's like every other word was "oh, sorry!"
每句话都是在跟人说"对不起"
Like a ticking time bomb.
到时候她就像定时炸弹那样
She was gonna come back and shoot this whole place up.
她一过来就把我这小店炸平了
Y'all, stop! Okay, look.
你们别笑了  好了  想想
I am going to--
我要
It's okay, it's okay. I'mma--
没事  没事  我会帮你
You know, I'mma make you look like a champion!
到时候  你看上去就是耀眼夺目的冠军
- Oh, yeah! Girls fight like, way harder than guys! - What?
-拳击场上女孩比男的打得都狠  -这样吗
Yeah, like, guys can go in, and they'll shake hands afterwards,
对  就比如  男人上场打拳  打完会握手
and they're all cool but girls, sometimes,
就很酷  但是有时候  女子拳击手就会
they hold a grudge. It's pretty nasty.
相互怀恨在心  让人厌恶
Mhm. I know that's right.
我能懂这种感觉
Well, Miss Champion. Viola!
冠军小姐  闪亮登场
Look at you!
快看呐
You like it?
喜欢吗
Sorry I'm late.
抱歉迟到了
I had to cover a shift for this bitch that got fired.
我得替那个被解雇的婊子顶班
Oh, no worries, it's fine. Look like it's getting late anyway.
不用担心  没关系  不过看起来也不早了
Nobody here but the usual suspects.
除了你们几个"常客"  也没别人
Oh, and the "female Rocky" over here!
对了  还有我们的女版"洛基"
Um, hey look, I would tip you if I had any money,
我身上没带钱  不然我定会给你小费的
but I just lost my job.
而且我最近还丢了工作
It's okay.
没关系的
And besides, Rosheen got you.
再说了  这些钱罗辛都帮你包了
Thank you.
谢谢你
What's going on?
怎么一回事
That's that crazy ass bitch with the mother.
这就是那个跟她妈妈一起住的疯婊子
- Oh! - Yeah!
-天呐  -没想到吧
The fuck did you just say?
你刚刚他妈的说什么
Bitch, you heard what I said, okay?
婊子  你听得一清二楚了  好吗
So take ya little ass outta here, alright?
所以赶紧给我滚出去  好吗
You not gon' do nothin'. You 'bout to do somethin'?
平时什么也不干  现在想干什么
You gon' do somethin'?
你想干什么吗
That's what I thought.
我想你也不敢
Get up.
站起来
- Oh no, you gotta go. - Alright, alright, alright.
-好了  你给我出去  -好的  好的  好的
- You do not fight in my place! - I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-不准在我的地盘上打架  -抱歉  抱歉
Sasha, what are you doi--
萨沙  你要干什
Hey, hey! Excuse me, Officer. Officer!
你好  你好  打扰一下  警官  警官
- What? - Can I get my phone call now, please?
-怎么了  -我现在能打个电话吗
I need to call someone.
我想找个人过来
Some type of medical emergency?
是需要急救吗
It is, actually. I need to see someone about my hand.
对的  我想找个医生过来检查下我的手
I think I might have broke it.
我觉得我的手好像是骨折了
Sir! Sir, sir. She lyin'.
先生  先生  她在撒谎
She always be lyin'. She ain't got no medical emergency.
她向来谎话连篇  她才不需要什么急救
I'm not lying! You can see that I might have broke my hand. Please.
我没有撒谎  你看我的手可能折了  拜托
Doesn't look that bad.
看起来没那么糟
Are you serious? I have a job tomorrow!
你在说笑吗  我明天还有正事要做
This is a very important job
非常重要的正事
that I need to get to, like, in a few hours, okay?
大概几个小时以后我就得赶过去  好吗
- She lyin'. - Please!
-她在说谎  -拜托你了
She lyin.' Her coochie is the only thing
她在撒谎  怕是她的"小妹妹"才有急症
that got a medical emergency, okay?
急着去见人  懂了吗
The gynecologist gon' need a chin strap
妇科医生怕是要用扣绳
to deal with that offense between her legs, okay?
绑在她两腿之间才能治好  懂了吗
That's good! I'm gonna tell the Captain about that one.
这个笑话不错  待会我和警长讲讲
You hear that, Nora? He's gonna tell 'em about
听到了吗  诺拉  他们以后就会讲起
your offence between your legs, bitch!
你腿间的罪行了  臭婊子
Man, I can't believe that you came to my work
我是真不敢相信你居然找上门来
and laid your hands on me, bitch.
还对我动手动脚  婊子
You are going to pay! This is not over, you hear me?
你要付出代价  我和你没完  听到了吗
This is on you!
全都怪你
Yeah. Why don't you
对啊  你怎么不
Why don't you go call one yo lil'
你为什么不打电话给你那些
Benz-drivin', BMW-havin',
开着奔驰  宝马的
bougie-ass hooker workers now, huh?
有钱有势的金主嫖客呢
Call 'em for that! Call! Call 'em!
给他们打电话啊  打啊  打给他们
Tell 'em to bail you outta jail,
求他们把你保释出去
see how fast they come!
看看他们来得能有多快
Uh, hey, Officer!
你好  警官
Hey! Hey! Please come here.
你好  拜托您过来一下
Am I allowed to use, uh, like my cell phone
我能否用一下我的手机
to get a number out of my phone
找一个号码
so that I can make my phone call?
然后我打一个电话
No.
不行
- Please? - No.
-拜托  -不行
I don't know his number by heart.
我记不太清他的号码
That's- that'd be my one phone call and that'll be it, I promise!
但我就打这一个电话  就一个  我保证
Goddamn, Nora!
该死的  诺拉
Have some respect for yourself.
你能不能有点尊严
Some decency!
活得体面些
You really gon' call one of them Johns
你真的要给那些男人们打电话
who be droppin' nickels in you?
用他们的臭钱  把你保释出去吗
He's not a J-- Uh.
他不是
It's a friend of mine. Please, I just don't know his number.
他是我朋友  拜托了  我只是记不清号码
You ain't got no friends. Stop lyin'.
你哪来的朋友  能不能说句真话听听
You ain't got to lie now! We here together, we in jail!
你不要再撒谎了  我们都在牢里蹲着呢
Look, please?
听着  拜托
Please?
拜托
Look, I'll see what I can do, alright?
听着  我看看我能做什么  好吗
Can you see what you can do for me, too? Laugh McGee?
你也能为我做些什么吗  爱笑的麦吉警官
Here's your numbers.
给你  你要的号码
Use our phone, dial nine for an outside line.
用我们的电话打  按9可以拨外线
Thank you.
谢谢您
Just call-- Just call him. It's fine.
就是  就是打个电话给他  没事的
Hi! You've reached Jason, and this is my phone!
你好  我是杰森  这是我的电话
Thank you so much for calling me.
非常感谢你的来电
I hope you are doing something wonderful with your days,
希望你最近过的顺心如意
and I know you are accomplishing something great!
我知道你正着手大事
Please leave a message,
请留言
and I will surely get back to you as soon as I can!
我一定会尽快给你回复的
Hey, uh, Jason. It's um-- I'm so sorry for calling you so late, um.
你好  杰森  很抱歉这么晚打电话给你
Or so early. I'm not, um-- But, uh, this is Nora.
或者说  抱歉这么早打给你  我是诺拉
Um, we met at the pharmacy.
我们是那天在药房认识的
Um, and you also came to my work.
你也来我工作的地方找过我
so uh, I needed to call, um, I'm in a little bit of a-- of a jam.
所以  我打给你是因为  我遇到了点麻烦
Um. You know that fight tournament that I- I had told you about?
你记得我跟你说过的拳击锦标赛吗
Luck of the redheads. Someone's posted bail.
我们的红发女子真幸运  有人保释你出去
Tell him never mind.
告诉他  谢谢
I can't be owin' anybody like that again.
我不能再欠别人人情了
OKay, Red. You got it. It's just that--
好的  红发妹  我会转达的  只是说
Oh, look! They makin' up nicknames for you here now.
哇  听听  他们现在都给你取了个爱称呢
Here you go, Red.
去吧  红发妹
Rich ass Captain Save-A-Ho is here!
我们有钱的"赎妓"队长来了
If it makes any difference,
保释你的不是什么有钱男人
it's not some rich ass guy.
如果告诉你  你会好受些的话
She's been shoveling all that cash in her pillowcase for years.
这么些年来  她一拿到现金就往枕套里藏
Mary,
玛丽
thank you.
谢谢你
Let's go.
另一只手
Nora, what the hell do I say about
诺拉  我怎么告诫你的
taking this shit outside the gym?
私人恩怨不要影响到我们的比赛
I know, it was really stupid.
我知道  这样真的很蠢
But it's not that bad, I swear.
但我发誓  没看上去那么糟
It's gonna be fine.
会好起来的
Everything else okay?
其他都还好吧
Yeah. Everything else is fine, yeah.
其他都很好  只是说
It's just this, it's just the knuckles.
只是伤到了指关节
Maybe you shouldn't do this today.
也许你今天不应该上场了
Please, Rosheen, I have to do this.
求你了  罗辛 我必须这么做
I don't have a choice. I have to fight today.
我别无选择  我今天一定要上场
It's really not that bad, I swear.
真的没那么糟  我发誓
Please.
拜托了
I'm messin' with you.
我逗你玩的
Me, stop you from fightin'?
我会阻止你参赛吗
They'd take my old ass out in the back alley
恐怕还没等我插手  他们就会把我
before that'd happen, right?
拖出后门暴打一顿  是不是
I don't know about that. I'd probably get my ass kicked.
那我倒不知道  不过我可能会被揍得很惨
Hey, nobody is ever a hundred percent goin' into a fight.
没人能百分之百投入战斗的
You're always gonna have a little somethin'
人们总会碰到些
that's really fucked up.
十分棘手的倒霉事
You just gotta fight through it, right?
挺过去就好了  对吗
Okay.
好啦
Give it. Spread 'em.
来  把手分开
Ladies and gentlemen, it doesn't look good
观众朋友们  看起来阿依莎情况
for Aisha. She's on the bottom.
不太乐观  她被压在了下面
No, no, she's turned it around,
不  不  她翻过来了
she's on the top! She's dominating!
她翻到了上面  重新掌握优势
They're back on their feet, they're back on their feet.
她们重新站起来了  她们站起来了
Alright, we're goin' in for some
好的  我们将看到一些
good Muay Thai exchanges here!
漂亮的泰拳对抗了
Good kick, good kick by Aisha!
踢得好  阿依莎踢得好
And it is over! Aisha knocked her out!
结束战斗  阿依莎把她拿下了
Nora Felix and Chase Alexander?
诺拉·费利克斯和蔡斯·亚历山大
You two are next. Five minutes.
你们俩下一组  五分钟准备
Kumite! Kumite!
来和我对打啊  来格斗啊
Great.
很好
One, two!
一  二
On to the next motherfuckin' round, Nora!
我晋级下一轮了  诺拉
When are you goin' up?
你什么时候上场
- Next. - Okay.
-下一组  -好啊
Well, good luck. Go get 'em. Go get 'em.
祝你好运  快去吧  快去
You're a fighter. That's why you're here.
你是一个战士  这就是你来此的原因
That's why you're fightin' and why you can fight
这就是你为何在战斗  以及你为何
all those things you're goin' through.
能与你所经历的一切抗争
Something got you here!
某些东西将你带来这里
Whether it was a reason or something--
无论是某个原因  还是
something that you're going through--
还是你正在经历的什么
that's what brought you here
正是它让你来到这里
and it's bringin' that out of you.
而现在是你释放的时候
You've gotta let it.
你需要把它释放出来
Nora.
诺拉
Mom?
妈妈
Nice Superman punch by Chase!
蔡斯超人般的一击
Nora looks like she's in trouble!
诺拉似乎陷入困境
Oh, man, it looks like Nora's in trouble.
天啊  诺拉好像不行了
She's gotta do something. She's gotta get up!
她必须做点什么  她必须得起来
Two good kicks to the ribs.
肋骨上两脚踢得不错
Nora's comin' back.
诺拉重新掌控了局面
Oh, man! There we go!
天啊  来吧
Nora's got her up against the cage. Utilizing that clench!
诺拉把她逼到笼壁了  锁死她
Throwing really good knees. I think she's in trouble--
膝盖踢得很猛  我觉得她不行了
Chase might be in trouble!
蔡斯要不行了
We got an eye gauge by Chase!
蔡斯插眼犯规
Break it up, break it up, break it up, break it up!
快分开  快分开  快分开  快分开
- Come on! - We're here to win a contest,
-住手  -你们是来参赛的
not hurt each other! Now let's go!
不是互相伤害的  走吧
The hell we've been through, no one can hurt you.
我们曾一起经历过磨难  没人能伤害你了
- Is Ms. Peters here yet? - No, not yet.
-彼得斯太太到了吗  -还没有
But she will be. Don't wait for her, honey.
不过她会来的  别等她了  宝贝
Just go! Go, go, go!
快走吧  走吧  走吧
Yeah, but I don't wanna leave you alone.
好吧  但我不想让你一个人待着
I'll be fine. Now give me a hug.
我没事的  来抱一下
Okay.
好的
I might lie down for a bit, anyway.
我可能要躺一会儿
Are you feeling okay?
你还好吗
I'm fine!
好着呢
You go kick ass!
去大干一场吧
I love you, kiddo.
我爱你  宝宝
I love you, too, Mom.
我也爱你  妈妈
How'm I doing?
我怎么样
Fuckin' horrible. But you're winnin'.
糟糕得要命  但你赢定了
Really?
真的吗
It's hard to see while you're in a fight,
你身处对抗中可能不觉得
but everyone else can see it.
但大家都看出来了
Now get in there and kick her ass.
现在回去  去把她拿下
You keep those hands up, you keep movin'.
双手时刻防卫  双脚不停移动
Alright? Spit it out.
记住了吗  吐出来
There you go. Alright. Let's go. Own it! C'mon!
很好  上场吧  完胜她  加油
Nora, you can't fight your way through everything.
诺拉  你不可能每件事都要斗到底
Yeah, well, it's not like I'm trying to fight, Mom.
是啊  妈妈  也不是我要斗的
It's just the way my life works.
我的生活就是这样的
Nora.
诺拉
Mom, I take care of you, don't I?
妈妈  我要照顾你  对吧
Yes.
对
And I make sure that you're not alone for too long.
我还要确保你不会独自待太长时间
And I make sure that I have food on the table every night
我每晚回家都要保证桌上有吃的
when I get home. For you.
保证你能吃上晚饭
And I make sure that I have your medicine.
我还得确保你有药吃
And I make sure that you have your scotch.
甚至保证你喝得上威士忌
And your crossword puzzles. Right?
玩得上填字游戏  对吧
So I don't understand. Why do you keep questioning me
我就不明白了  你为什么总在质疑
on what I'm trying to do?
我在做什么
And how I'm living my life?
还有我怎么生活
You know, I'm trying my best!
我已经尽力了
This is the best I can do.
这是我能做的最好的了
No, one's giving me these things.
这一切都不是白来的
I love you! Is that not enough?
我爱你  这还不够吗
It's always been enough.
这对我永远是最满足的
You fight and fight.
你不停地奋斗
You're good at it. Like I was.
做得不错  就像我当初一样
But, there are just certain things you're gonna need to accept.
但是  有些事情你只能接受
- I can't talk to you. This is-- - Nora!
-我没法和你说了  这是  -诺拉
Came all this way. For what?
我费了这么大劲  图什么
It's okay--
没关系的
It's not okay. It's not okay, guys!
有关系  一点都不好
Alright, it's not too bad.
好了  你状态还不错
You're in good shape for your next fight.
可以继续下一场比赛
Wait, I won?
等等  我赢了吗
You keep talkin' like this and I will stop the next fight.
你再问我就不让你参赛了
No, wait, Rosheen. I'm sorry.
不  等等  罗辛  我很抱歉
I'm-- Yeah, I'm, I'm good.
我  我很好
Alright. I'm kiddin'. You're there.
好啦  我开玩笑的  你当然没问题
Here. Let's go. You got this, kid.
给  咱们走  孩子你没问题的
Breathe.
呼吸
My little Nora.
我的小诺拉
All grown up.
都长成大姑娘了
But you still fit into my arms.
可我还是能把你抱住
Do you remember sleeping like this when your father...
你还记从前咱们也这样睡  那时你爸爸还
We were both just babies. All curled up into a little ball.
咱俩都像小宝宝一样  缩成一小团
Yeah, I remember.
是啊  我记得
You were so warm.
你暖暖的
And your hair tickled my nose.
小头发轻挠着我的鼻子
You were my little angel.
你就是我的小天使
You saved my life back then.
是你挽救了我的一生
I saved?
我挽救你了吗
When your father couldn't hack it with my ornery ass anymore,
当你爸再也受不了我的暴脾气时
you were the only thing that kept me going.
你成为我生活唯一的动力
You were the only reason I had
你是我每天早上起床
to get up every morning and carry on.
继续生活下去的唯一理由
Because I had to take care of you.
因为我得照顾你
So,
所以说
I understand what you're doing for me right now. I really do.
我明白你现在为我做的一切  我真的明白
Mom?
妈妈
I'm not proud of what I had to do--
这是我应该做的事  我并不引以为傲
Your father used to say
你爸常说
"A woman sees the world the way the woman sees it."
"女人啊  都是头发长见识短"
And that way, I would know that he was drunk,
他一这样  我就知道他喝多了
and I would punch him in the goddamn neck.
我会揍他脖子
Yeah. Fun scene for a child
是啊  这场面可不是每个小孩
to grow up in. I remember.
都能看到的  我当然记得
Well, certainly toughened you up.
这也让你变得坚强
- It's a tough world. - Yeah.
-人世多艰  -没错
It's a tough world.
人世多艰
I think there's still a dent in the wall in the kitchen
厨房的墙上现在还留着个凹痕
from when you threw him.
就是你当时扔他时留下的
Well, I had to hurt him so that he didn't hurt me first.
我先伤害他  他才不会伤害我
And in the end, he still did.
可到头来  他还是伤害了我
Sometimes, I wish I could have stepped
有时候  我真希望自己当初
into his shoes back then.
能从他的角度想想
'Cause I would have seen how messed up he was,
那样我就知道他的处境有多糟糕了
and I would have walked out that door,
那样我就会选择离开
holding you in my arms.
抱着你一起离开
Life is a fight, maybe, Nora.
也许生活是场战斗  诺拉
But you don't have to hurt everyone around you.
但你不必伤害周围的每一个人
You can just walk away.
你径自走开就好了
'Cause there, there are other ways to win.
因为人生不止一条道路
You are a beautiful, strong woman.
你是一个美丽而坚强的女人
And I am so proud of you.
我真为你骄傲
And I'm gonna miss you so goddamn much when I go.
我要是离去了  肯定会非常想你的
How the hell'd the judges not see me
裁判就没看到吗
whoop your ass for three rounds?
我揍了你整整三轮
I had your ass, bitch!
我把你打得落花流水
And you know it! This was my fight!
而且你很明白  这场是我的比赛
- You fuckin' rigged somethin' around here - Hey!
-你他妈的在这里做了手脚  -别吵了
Jane, get the hell out of here! It's over!
简  出去  都结束了
Get outta here!
赶紧走
We won again?
我们又赢了吗
You're in one hell of a zone.
你打得真挺辛苦的
Yeah.
是啊
But you took a few good shots.
不过有几击很不错
Here, lemme close some of those cuts up.
来  我给你处理下伤口
Here, put your head back.
坐过来  把头仰过去
Hold on.
稍等
Alright, hold it still.
好了  仰着别动
Lemme get this; I don't want it to split back open.
我给你处理下  可别再裂开了
One more fight.
最后一场
We good, Rosheen.
没事  罗辛
Always got my girl's corner, anyway.
反正我永远挺我媳妇
Is that right?
是吗
Rosheen, we good. She doesn't have anybody, anyway.
罗辛  没事  她也没人可以依靠
- Damn right. - Babe. Be nice, man.
-不能再对了  -亲爱的  友好点
If I was gonna lose to anybody,
如果我打输了
it'd be you, Aisha.
阿依莎  那一定是输给你
Aisha, she's trying to get into your head.
阿依莎  她忽悠你呢
Don't listen to her.
别理她
Are you okay to go on?
你还能再继续吗
Rosheen, I told you, I cannot quit. I gotta--
罗辛  我说过了  我不能退出  我得
I'm messin' with you!
我逗你玩呢
There ain't an ounce of quit in you.
你一点也没有放弃的意思
But you know damn good and well Aisha can knock people out.
可阿依莎的实力多强你一清二楚
Or she can rip your arm out.
她没准会把你胳膊扯下来
I need you to focus and stay focused,
你必须要专心  保持精神集中
'cause I don't know where the hell your head's at today.
真搞不懂你今天到底在想什么
It's been a weird day.
这一天都怪怪的
The hell we've been through, no one can hurt you.
我们曾一起经历过磨难  没人能伤害你了
- Is Ms. Peters here yet? - No, not yet.
-彼得斯来了吗太太  -还没有
But don't wait for her, honey. Just, just go!
别等她了  宝贝  快走吧
Go, go, go!
走吧  走吧
Mom, I don't wanna leave you alone.
妈妈  我不想留你独自待着
I will be fine. Now you give me a hug and a kiss.
我没事的  来抱一下  亲一个
I may lay down for a bit.
我可能要躺一会儿
Are you okay?
你还好吗
Yep! Just a proud mama!
好得很  也骄傲得很
You go kick ass!
去大干一场吧
I love you, kiddo.
我爱你  宝宝
I love you, too, Ma.
我也爱你  妈妈
Alright, the two are at center.
好的  她们来到了赛场中央
You can see the tension in their--
能感受到她们之间的紧张气氛
- Yeah. - Between their coaches.
-没错  -教练之间也是
Aisha looks ready to go. She looks ready to pounce.
阿依莎已经准备好  随时出击
- Nora looks-- Relaxed. - Yeah.
-诺拉看起来很放松  -是的
- Alright, touch gloves. - Gettin' ready to break,
-好的  互碰一下拳套  -准备开战
touchin' gloves, and here we go!
互碰拳套  开始
Wait, guys! No, wait, something's happening!
等下  伙计们  不  等等  有事要发生
Yeah, it is! A fight! Now, get out there and fight!
对  是有事  有比赛呢  快去迎战
C'mon, Nora! Get your hands up! C'mon!
加油  诺拉  把手举起来  加油
Oh shit.
该死
Nora could be tappin' out any second. She's kind of...
tap out：快速拍击地面或对手身躯三次表示认输
She's gonna tap!
她要认输了
C'mon, Nora, get out of her! Roll out!
加油  诺拉  摆脱掉她  翻身挣脱
- She's kind of... - She's gonna tap, she's gonna tap!
-她有点  -她不行了  要认输了
C'mon, Nora! Roll out of it! Roll out of it!
加油  诺拉  翻身挣脱  翻身挣脱
What a reversal!
好一个反败为胜
There you go! Yes! Yes! Yes!
就这样  漂亮  好极了 太棒了
She's got her back turned again!
她竟然翻过来了
What are you doing? Get out there!
你在干什么  快离开那
Come on now!
上啊
Turn around!
转过身去
Nora, don't!
诺拉  别这样
Get out there! Go get her! Go get her!
冲上去  打败她  打败她
- There it is. - That's what's happening right now.
-她冲上去了  -这就是当前赛况
Protect yourself! Get your arms up!
防守啊  抬起胳膊
No, come on! Come on, Nora, you gotta fight!
振作点  挺住  诺拉  你要反击
This what you want? This what you really want?
这就是你想要的  这就是你梦寐以求的
Come on! Watch your shoulder! No!
加把劲  注意你的肩膀  别受伤
Come on! Come on!
加油  加油
Nora, get outta that!
诺拉  快挣脱
Nora, tap!
诺拉  认输吧
She's gotta do something.
她必须得做点什么了
If she doesn't do anything, this fight is over.
如果她什么都不做  就胜负分明了
Come on!
认输吧
- Her shoulder. It's about ready to go. - That right arm.
-她的肩膀  感觉快脱臼了  -右臂
That right arm. Is she gonna tap?
那只右臂  她会认输吗
Oh my God! The arm snapped!
我的天啊  一方选手手臂脱臼了
Aw, shit!
完蛋了
Are the refs gonna do anything? Her arm!
如果裁判认为这回合已经变成"一边倒" 或者在比赛进行中一方拳手严重受伤，将会停止比赛
She's still in the fight! Is the ref gonna stop this?
她还在拳台上  裁判会终止比赛吗
- He should. - I don't know if he's going to.
-他应该会  -我不知道他会不会
Why didn't you stop it?
你为什么不终止比赛
She didn't tap.
她没有拍垫认输
Ref, she didn't tap out! She didn't tap out!
裁判  她没有认输  她没有拍垫认输
- She didn't tap. - Stop it! Stop it!
-她确实没有  -终止比赛  快终止
You good? Fight! Let's go.
你还能行吗  比赛  继续
Aight, baby, c'mon! Finish this off! Right now!
好了宝贝  上吧  赶紧赢了这场比赛
What do I do?
我该怎么做
Finish it off, finish her off!
赢了比赛  赢了她
She's there for the taking, baby! C'mon, go get her!
她无力还击了  上吧  宝贝  赢了她
Ref, stop it! What are you doing?
裁判  结束比赛  你愣着干嘛
What are you doing?
终止比赛
Nora, you better stop.
诺拉  你最好停下
Get outta here, Nora.
离开拳台  诺拉
Nora, get the fuck out of here.
诺拉  别硬撑了
I think the ref should stop this fight.
我认为裁判应该叫停这场比赛
She's not even playing, not defense.
她已经没法进攻了  连防守都没有
Arm, again.
又是针对手臂的招式
There is the other...
这次是另一边
Is she gonna tap?
她会认输吗
Keep breathing, keep breathing, kid! Keep breathing!
保持呼吸  保持呼吸  孩子  保持呼吸
C'mon Nora! Roll out of it, roll out of it!
加把劲  诺拉  翻身挣脱  翻身挣脱
Atta girl, atta girl! Woo! Yes!
好样的  就这样  太棒了
Get on top! Get her knee, take her knees!
占据上位  膝盖  伤她的膝盖
Take her knee, Nora!
控制住她的膝盖  诺拉
Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
对  就这样  就这样  好极了
Okay, alright. Oh my God, the tables have turned here!
好吧  我的天啊  局势再次反转
So now, Nora has Aisha in a really tight knee lock.
阿依莎的膝盖现在被诺拉紧紧锁住
- Yeah, Aisha's in trouble, now. This is... - Yes!
-是的  阿依莎有麻烦了  真是  -就这样
Is this gonna take the fight?
这招会一锤定音吗
I couldn't believe she's still going.
她伤成这样居然还能继续比赛
I have not seen a fight like this in years!
真是一场难得一见的比拼
C'mon, baby! C'mon! Get out, get out!
加油宝贝  挺住  翻身挣脱出来
Get out, roll over!
挣脱出来  翻身
Come on. This is incredible!
天呐  太不可思议了
Nora's still got her. There's...
诺拉仍然控制着对手  这简直
Saved by the bell.
铃响得很及时
That was an incredible first round. Unbelievable.
精彩的第一回合  难以置信
It looked like Nora was done from the get-go.
感觉诺拉从一开始就拼命了
Like completely out of it,
像是全然不顾了
turning to her corner, turning her back.
面对强势的对手  从下位顽强翻身
- A massive amount of heart on both girls, here. - Yeah.
-这两位选手身体素质都很好  -是的
What a fight!
真是一场激烈的缠斗
But lack of D, on both, I would say.
但我觉得  两位选手都缺少防守
Yeah, I would say so.
是  我也这么觉得
- There's a lot of offense, not a lot of defense. - Yeah.
-进攻较多  防守较少  -对
Almost a couple submissions.
还有几个压制性动作
Work on the defense a bit.
应该在防守上再下点功夫
Way to survive that round, kid.
上一场能赢很不容易了  孩子
Now, he's gonna have to pop it in now, okay?
现在医生要把你的手臂归位  好吗
Alright. Take a deep breath.
好吧  深吸一口气
You got it. Look at me. C'mon.
你能行的  看着我  来吧
Relax, relax. Breathe, breathe, breathe!
放松  放松  保持呼吸  呼吸
Okay, right here.
好的  就这儿
- Oh, shit! - You're good!
-该死  -你很棒
- Is it in? - Okay, okay.
-归位了吗  -好的
I can't keep doing this. I can't keep going.
我坚持不下去了  我撑不住了
That's okay, Nora. It's okay. It's not a problem.
没关系  诺拉  没事的  这不是问题
That was a hell of a fight!
上一回合确实很艰险
No, no, you don't understand.
不  不  你不明白
I think my mom, she's gonna commit suicide.
我觉得我妈妈  她可能要自杀
Nora, you... your mom's gone.
诺拉  你  你妈妈已经去世了
How did you know? When did you find out? Wha...?
你怎么知道的  什么时候的事
Honey, she passed away two months ago.
亲爱的  她两个月前就去世了
No! No, that's not... No! No, no, no, no!
不  不  不可能  怎么可能  不会的
That's not, that's not possible!
不会的  那是不可能的
Hey, hey, hey. I was at the funeral, remember?
我还参加了葬礼  记得吗
And... Yeah, and it took like, over a month for your...
还有  你的脚被玻璃扎伤了
for your feet to heal from the glass cuts, you remember?
过了一个多月才好  你记得吗
No! No, this can't be right!
不  不  这不可能
Take a deep breath!
深呼吸
- You got it. - Take it easy.
-你能行的  -放轻松
Mary...
玛丽
Thank you.
谢谢你
I just saw her! I just saw her this morning!
我才见过她啊  今天早上还见了
I... You guys, this isn't right! No!
你们搞错了吧  不是你们说的那样
You feeling okay?
你还好吗
I love you too, Mom.
我也爱你  妈妈
I saved?
我挽救了你吗
I'm not proud of what I had to do.
这是我应该做的事  我并不引以为傲
You're gonna kick my ass, but I'm gonna stop this.
就算你要打我  我也得让你清醒过来
No, no, no, please! Don't do that! Please! I can do this!
不  不  不用  拜托  我能继续比赛
Look, I know you're right!
听着  我知道你是对的
You... It was two months ago.
那是两个月前的事了
I remember, it was two months ago.
我知道  那是两个月前的事了
I can do this.
我能行的
I'm gonna do it for her. I have to finish. I have to!
我要为了她赢了这场比赛  我必须这么做
Nora, it's okay. We're just gonna walk away.
诺拉  如果你想退出比赛也没关系的
I gotta do this. I gotta do this for her.
我必须这么做  既是为她
I gotta do this for me. I gotta do this!
也是为了我自己  我必须这么做
C'mon.
加油
You ready? Okay.
准备好了吗  好的
I can't, I can't! I can't. I can't do this.
不行  不行  我不行  我做不到
C'mon! C'mon.
站起来  你可以的
- Okay, get up. - I can't. I can't.
-好了  起来  -我不行  我做不到
What are you gonna do here? Are you okay to continue?
准备好了吗  还能继续比赛吗
One second, please. Thank you.
请稍等  谢谢
I can't hear you.
我听不清你说话
Can't hear you.
我听不清
Mom, I can't hear you.
妈妈  我听不见你说的
I'm gonna stop the fight.
我们退出比赛
- No! Please! No, no, no, no! Please, no! - Come on.
-不  不要  拜托  不要  -没关系的
What do I do?
我该怎么办
Mom, what do I do?
妈妈  我该怎么做
Fuck it!
去他妈的
It's okay.
没关系
No, fuck it!
不  去他妈的
You know, you said
你自己之前说
that you never go into a fight one hundred percent,
比赛之前永远不可能百分之百准备好
and you said that you never face life at one hundred percent
也不可能总是以最好的状态面对生活
because it's all just bullshit, right? You said that!
因为总会有扯淡的事发生  对吧  你说的
I said that. Are you sure you wanna do this?
我说过  你确定要继续吗
No.
不确定
This is stupid!
这太蠢了
Fuck!
妈的
I'm fuckin' with you!
我唬你呢
Yeah, she's good! We're in.
好吧  她好了  我们参加下一轮
We're back! Alright. Alright.
我们回来了  好了  好了
Plus, you don't wanna let down your super fan over there.
另外  你也不想让你的铁杆粉丝失望吧
Nora! No-ra! No-ra! No-ra! No-ra!
诺拉  诺拉  诺拉  诺拉
No-ra!
诺拉
- Come on, champ. Let's go. - No-ra! No-ra!
-来吧  冠军  我们上  -诺拉  诺拉
And we're back for the second round of this fight here, but...
让我们回到这场比赛的第二轮  但是
- What? - Fuck you, it's over?
-什么情况  -他妈的  结束了吗
Wait, wait, what happened? What do you mean the fight's over?
等等  发生了什么  什么叫比赛结束了
Bullshit! What the fuck?
乱搞什么  怎么回事
- I'm good! - Man, I told you she was good!
-我很好  -裁判  我说过  她好着呢
She didn't come out of this...
她可不会退出
Woah! The ref! He's wavin' his hands! Hold on!
裁判在挥舞他的手  等下
Woah, woah, red corner quit. Red corner quit!
红方退出了  是红方
The judge is yelling red corner has withdrawn.
裁判宣布红方退出了比赛
Let's try here. Alright.
试着动一下这里  好了
I'm okay.
我没事
We need to get her out of here.
我们得让她离开这
She worked too hard for this.
她努力都白费了
No. No, no, no, no.
不行  不  不能这样
You can't give this to me.
你不能把冠军拱手让人
I didn't. I can't. It's my knee.
我没有  我也做不到  我膝盖受伤了
I'm fucked up.
我失败了
I'm not gonna let you just quit, then.
我不会让你就这样放弃的
I didn't quit.
我没有放弃
I'll win next time.
我下次会赢
But you won. This was all you.
但这次你赢了  赢得很彻底
Got a weird way to fuckin' do it.
用你自己的一套就他妈赢了
But this was all you.
但确实是你赢了
C'mere.
靠近点
I can't get to you.
我够不到你
I love you.
我爱你
Well, it looks like the red corner has withdrawn.
好吧  看起来红方已经退出了
Is that the official word?
这是官方的说法吗
And it looks like Nora... Nora has won.
这样的话诺拉  诺拉赢了
This is your moment. Fuckin' take that shit in.
这是属于你的时刻  好好享受吧
This fight, unbelievable. Nora!
这场比赛  真是令人难以置信  诺拉
Congratulations to the new champ!
祝贺这位新生冠军
Crazy comeback, wow!
疯狂的回归
Wow, what an evening.
令人难忘的夜晚
Yeah I can't believe that just happened!
是啊  我真不敢相信她赢了
That's my girl!
这才是我的姑娘
You know what?
你知道吗
You showed up, you worked hard,
从你来到训练馆  一直以来的努力训练
you did it.
今天终于成功了
No-ra! No-ra!
诺拉  诺拉
We did it.
是我们成功了
You did all the hard work, sweetheart.
是你自己刻苦训练  亲爱的
I just did a lot of yellin'.
我只是不停在旁边嚷嚷
- Right? - You're good at yelling, that's for sure.
-对吧  -你确实很擅长"嚷嚷"
Hey, I know that's real.
我知道我擅长
You okay, champ?
你还好吧  冠军
Yeah, I'm all good.
嗯  我很好
♪ So give me one more day ♪
♪ 再给我一天时间 ♪
♪ Give me one more way ♪
♪ 去寻找一条路线 ♪
♪ I swear I can handle the pain ♪
♪ 让我学会忍受痛苦 ♪
♪ Then you're free to walk away ♪
♪ 即使你已不在身边 ♪
♪ Give me one more day ♪
♪ 再给我一天时间 ♪
♪ Give me one more way ♪
♪ 去寻找一条路线 ♪
♪ To feel the pain I'm in ♪
♪ 让你感受我的痛苦 ♪
♪ Then you're free to walk away ♪
♪ 即使你已远在天边 ♪
♪ But give me one day ♪
♪ 请再给我一天时间 ♪
♪ Before you choose to fade away ♪
♪ 在你离开之前 ♪